#### Contact

katully23@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kimberly-potts-6b224944 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Nursing Hospitals Inpatient

Certifications

Basic Life Support Instructor

CNOR

# Kimberly Potts

Perioperative Clinical Development Specialist at MD Anderson Cancer Center West Houston

Houston, Texas Area

# Summary

Experienced registered nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in perioperative nursing specialties including: Gynecology, Pediatrics, Urology, Robotics, and Cardiothoracic surgery. Strengths in nursing and staff education, educational program development, quality improvement projects and nursing management. Maintains current CNOR and ACLS certification.

## Experience

MD Anderson Cancer Center 18 years 3 months

Perioperative Clinical Development Specialist May 2016 - Present (4 years 1 month)

Clinical Nurse

May 2010 - May 2016 (6 years 1 month)

Coordinate the care of patients undergoing surgery in the Main operating room. My primary specialty of operating room nursing is Gynecology, Urology, Pediatrics, thoracic and robotic surgery.

Lab Technician August 2008 - May 2010 (1 year 10 months)

Tissue Procurement Specialist March 2002 - August 2008 (6 years 6 months)

### Education

Grand Canyon University

Master of Science in Nursing Leadership (2015 - 2017)

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2008 - 2009)

Houston Community College · (2004 - 2008)